<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on AFC Roza</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on AFC Roza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023/24 - Our Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2324-sofar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2324-sofar/</guid>
      <description>2023/24 - Our Season So Far After finishing second in our first ever season in Division 6 of the Barnet Sunday Football League, we were handed a sizeable promotion up to Division 1. This entailed a climb from the 8th tier to the 3rd tier of the BSFL pyramid, meaning that we had a big challenge on our hands. Here&amp;rsquo;s how we&amp;rsquo;ve got on so far&amp;hellip;&#xA;September After much anticipation, September was upon us and our first fixture was an away one against AFC Rose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - AFC Oakwood (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oakwood_a_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oakwood_a_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Oakwood (A) Sunday morning&amp;rsquo;s setting was Oakhill Park: somewhere that, despite being an away fixture, felt very much at home for AFC Roza. We had trained there during pre-season for the last couple of years, and many of us had experience there on matchdays as well; and you could see that the boys were comfortable in their surroundings from the moment we arrived.&#xA;In terms of the league table, this was an extremely valuable fixture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - AFC Oakwood (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oakwood_a_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oakwood_a_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Oakwood (A) Going in hopeful against a side who we had beat last season, we fell to a humiliating 6-0 defeat to top-of-the-league AFC Oakwood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - AFC Rose (H)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/afcrose_h_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/afcrose_h_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - AFC Rose (H) A sunny Sunday morning in North London was the setting, with a ‘Rose Derby’ on the agenda. The game was delicately poised, with a win for either side making all the difference towards the top end of the table. Both teams came with significant support, and the game didn’t disappoint.&#xA;Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Eric Schmidt, Giorgio Koullas, Chris Johnson, Jake Koumi; Michael Georgiades, Danny Smith, Saj Rajaratnam; Iddo Razin, Steph Savva, Alex Andreou&#xD;AFC Roza, in pink, started fast and on the front foot, and got a goal inside 10 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Barnet Borough (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/barnetborough_a_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/barnetborough_a_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Barnet Borough (A) AFC Roza were back in action on Sunday, hoping that last week&amp;rsquo;s cancellation would not disrupt the strong run of form that we had been in over recent weeks. Although this was an away fixture, Barnet Borough are one of the teams who share the same home pitch as Roza - so it was familiar territory in the form of Enfield Powerleague.&#xA;There were a number of high profile absentees in the Roza squad including Chris Johnson, Iddo Razin and Eric Schmidt, but the boys were at least boosted by Ben Reynolds&amp;rsquo; return to the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Continental (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conti_a_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conti_a_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Continental (A) After two unfortunate results, where Roza harshly lost by one goal on consecutive occasions, Sunday was a test of mental strength as well as footballing quality for the boys - as we faced FC Continental. It was to be played on a muddy, wet Enfield Playing Fields; and with three games left of the season going into this one, the points on offer were extremely valuable ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Continental (H)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conti_h_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conti_h_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Continental (H) It was a gloomy, windy home fixture for The Rose - the visitors today, Continental. Roza began today’s fixture at 3rd in the league and with the opportunity to leapfrog AFC Oakwood, we were eager to make a statement to the rest of the league.&#xA;Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Rees Colgan, Giorgio Koullas, Chris Johnson, Jake Koumi; Michael Georgiades, Danny Smith, Saj Rajaratnam; Iddo Razin, Steph Savva, Alex Andreou&#xD;A strong first 10 minutes was characterised by dynamic and slick Rozaball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Enfield Club de Futbol (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/enfieldcdf_a_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/enfieldcdf_a_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Enfield Club de Futbol (A)&#xD;Dramatic circumstances secured a victory for Roza in the previous game, but Enfield Club de Futbol were a brand new challenge to face on Sunday 27th October. We travelled to Clowes Sports Ground with a strong squad hopeful of leaving with 3 points.&#xA;Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Harry Small, Chris Johnson, Jake Koumi, Ollie Begueria; Danny Smith, Ben Reynolds, Moh Kataria; Iddo Razin, Steph Savva, Alex Andreou&#xD;In the early stages of the game, chances were few and far between with both teams struggling to hold onto the ball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Fireside (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fireside_a_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fireside_a_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Fireside (A) As games up and down the country were postponed due to torrential rain, we were pleasantly surprised by the news that our away game against Fireside would go ahead on Sunday. With a few absentees, including both goalkeepers, we knew we had a tough test; but we were keen to find 3 points against a team who beat us earlier in the season.&#xA;Roza set up with a midfield diamond, a throwback to the 22/23 season where this system paid dividends in their journey to second place in the table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Highgate Albion 2s (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hafc_a_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hafc_a_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Highgate Albion 2s (A) Following a huge win against a dangerous side in AFC Oakwood, the Roza were out in force again against a strong Highgate Albion. The 2 teams, sat keenly in second and third before today’s fixture, knew a result would be definitive in terms of this seasons standings.&#xA;Starting XI: Nicholas Christou; Deano Spyrou, Terry Savva, Chris Johnson, Rees Colgan; Michael Georgiades, Saj Rajaratnam, Danny Smith; Ben Reynolds, Steph Savva, Alex Andreou&#xD;Roza, playing in their blue away strip, started slow and struggled to play out from the back, playing up a steep hill in the first half.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Highgate Albion 2s (H)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/highgate_h_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/highgate_h_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Highgate Albion 2s (H) As winter starts to approach, a gloomy Mount Grace was the setting for a crucial encounter against a familiar opponent on Sunday. With just one position and no love lost between these two teams last season, we knew that this fixture - now being played in the league above - would be a close one, and one that would require a level of combativeness if we were to come away with anything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Komi Kebir (A)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/komi_a_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/komi_a_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Komi Kebir (a) In an exciting but tense encounter, AFC Roza took a trip down the A10 to face Komi Kebir at their home pitch, Enfield Playing Fields. This all-Greek clash felt like a big affair, albeit early in the season.&#xA;Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Rees Colgan, Giorgio Koullas, Chris Johnson, Jake Koumi; Danny Smith, Saj Rajaratnam, Ben Reynolds; Michael Andreou, Steph Savva, Alex Andreou&#xD;The match began slowly, with both teams sharing possession and the majority of play occurring in the midfield - neither side managed to create significant chances early on, leading to a cagey start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - New World (H)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/newworld_h_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/newworld_h_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - New World (H) On a wet and cold September morning, AFC Roza faced a confident New World side who had won both their opening fixtures of the season. Despite the challenging conditions, the pitch held up well, with the ball zipping across the surface. The atmosphere was tense as both teams aimed to assert their dominance early on.&#xA;*Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Deano Spyrou, Giorgio Koullas, Terry Savva, Rees Colgan; Danny Smith, Ben Reynolds, Sajith Rajaratnum; Alex Andreou, Steph Savva, Iddo Razin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - RT United (h)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rt_utd_h_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rt_utd_h_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - RT United (h) In a fixture where two teams had never met before, AFC Roza hosted bottom of the league RT United at Mount Grace School. Looking to improve their current form, and put last week’s poor result behind them, there was a mutual “must win” vibe around the camp.&#xA;Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Harry Small, Chris Johnson, Jake Koumi, Ollie Begueria; Danny Smith, Ben Reynolds, Moh Kataria; Iddo Razin, Steph Savva, Alex Andreou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - RT United (h)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rt_utd_h_cup_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rt_utd_h_cup_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - RT United (h) A bright and dry November&amp;rsquo;s Sunday morning at Mount Grace (not often we say that) was the setting for this weekend&amp;rsquo;s fixture. In what was a huge pre-game bonus for both teams, the Home Ground staff had actually remembered to paint some lines on the pitch! Unfortunately, they forgot to get the lawn mower out, but baby steps.&#xA;Starting XI: Rajan Ranu; Terry Savva, Chris Johnson, Ollie Begueria; Michael Georgiades, Danny Smith, Ben Reynolds, Saj Rajaratnam; Iddo Razin, Steph Savva, Michael Andreou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Trent Park (H)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/trent_h_2324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/trent_h_2324/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Trent Park (H) It was a freezing Sunday morning, but the Roza boys certainly heated up our Enfield Powerleague home pitch with an excellent performance against Trent Park. With Trent Park being an established side and going into the fixture in second place, it was a tough test for Roza who had lost three in a row going either side of Christmas; but it was a test that the boys passed with flying colours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match Report - Trent Park (H)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/trent_h_2425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/trent_h_2425/</guid>
      <description>Match Report - Trent Park (H) As the 24/25 BSFL Season made it&amp;rsquo;s long-awaited introduction, the setting was our new home pitch: Mount Grace School. The boys had been training hard ahead of the campaign, so this fixture couldn&amp;rsquo;t come sooner. A mild morning entailed the visit of familiar opponents in Trent Park, so we knew what was ahead of us as we aimed to earn our first three points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miyagi Bonsai Player of the Month: February &#39;24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mbpotm-feb24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mbpotm-feb24/</guid>
      <description>Player of the Month: February 2024 And the Miyagi Bonsai Player of the Month for February 2024 is&amp;hellip;&#xA;Michael Georgiades! As one of the founding fathers, Michael G has always had a big part to play within the club off the pitch - but his influence on it has come leaps and bounds in recent months. He has established himself as a mainstay at the heart of the Roza engine room, and his combative nature combined with his composure has helped Roza throughout the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miyagi Bonsai Player of the Month: January &#39;24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mbpotm-jan24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mbpotm-jan24/</guid>
      <description>Player of the Month: January 2024 And 2024&amp;rsquo;s first Miyagi Bonsai Player of the Month is&amp;hellip;&#xA;Giorgio Koullas! Giorgio has been an absolute rock at the heart of the Roza defence this month, commanding the back line with strong leadership and astute defending throughout. The team&amp;rsquo;s defensive cohesion has looked increasingly settled as the month has gone on, and Koullas&amp;rsquo; emerging centre-back partnership with Chris Johnson is certainly one of the main reasons for this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miyagi Bonsai Player of the Month: November &#39;23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mbpotm-nov23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mbpotm-nov23/</guid>
      <description>Player of the Month: November 2023 And your November 2023 Miyagi Bonsai Player of the Month is&amp;hellip;&#xA;Cal Cook! Following in the footsteps of our first ever Player of the Month Steph Savva, our American attacking midfielder Cal Cook took the award for November.&#xA;Cal had an excellent month in November, playing only 2 of our 3 fixtures but scoring 3 goals and assisting once in the process. His brace against PS Birlikspor helped us to a 4-0 win, in a game where he was causing problems for the defence throughout.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
